As the man of God prophet TB Joshua moved along the rows at the Monday live prophetic service he prays for visitors from other countries
breaking generational curses and rewriting family histories in the name of Jesus Christ
During [the] prayer this lady cried out bringing her complaint to the man of God. I'm stranded
I'm from seraphic
[Erin] [if] mine AtSuko Kazuki to copy you are nominated and
Romantic question the holy spirit is a senior you less Sata, Freaka
Purposely, you got a visa to which country not nigeria [too] well so can I came with my boyfriend in
Kinda he tell me day, so I came here to find [away] because nobody what happen Ghana he left me
You didn't have [mine] while he left you
He was having a girlfriend
So he just left me off, but you left South Africa because you want to marry him. Yes
I thought you will marry me, and we [took] business David there were so many
You're less at Africa because you want traditional into the ocean yes, okay? What happened in see Ghana a coach stranded
I was calling his phone. I was thinking also, we stayed there for [like] three [years]
We are staying in another house, so he couldn't pay the money so he left me he said doesn't have money
Why are you no talking? I see you came from South Africa to Maggie. I'm trying to explain because if I can't okay [I]
Came to kind of from connect image you a lot of set your own my [bad] girl
You know you're a bad girl
You know that?
Yes, until [you] accept your own yes, and you accept that you are bad girl
Yes
You are the people that's prolly the name of your country
You have not been shown the reason why you people separated your father has not given you a concept to marry the boy
You are not on the property you left your home
Follow man you disappoint your parents
Now she has realized a mistake. She
Just want to collect money from man. Oh, God Monica. I'm stranded. [I'm] [raymond] about the street
I need money to go bad so Monica will give you money, and you know a Mammogram must know who you are
What a beautiful lady
What is your problem [you]?
[are] now facing your septum to man is a romantic to be looking for you
Opposite is [not] the case
Your mother you see yes, because of you because they are looking for you
My name is [Ala]. [Moana] [ZI] I'm from South Africa during the service on Monday
[I] cry out to the men of God. I told him they some stranded the prophesy dates. I'm a bad girl
I just left my country without telling my parents, and it's true. It's all started in South Africa
You know I didn't tell my [parents] who I am going I just lied to them
I may cry two ways in [I] [have] a degree in criminology
So I met this guy he promised me that who [come] so kind and then you give me mine
I run away with him
I saw my parents that I am working where I'm working out by sending them mine every month
He took me to kinda and then when we reached to kind of we a lurch in herself
He kept me in the hotel for two years who will come in cinema during the night
So I
Keep I kept believing that one table will give me money [so] as he promised me in seraphic
He was pissing me were always quarreling. He told me that I'm a pet black kid every time since he met me [there] [is] just
Disappointment, and you know things are not going well in their life, so I he left me and then I was Australia
I didn't know as to - I was going from enzo men
Sleeping in the streets [mosquitoes] itil, you know as to in Guilin I
Came to know about Samana [LCV]
I didn't know I didn't have - who came here
But the passengers in day a flower station in [Kinda] helpless who came here when I came here. I was trying because
every time also overcome my problems
[stupid] trunk so less. I can't be confident and face people so I came here on Sunday
I was trying
I was writing the ashes I was drinking our strong contacts who?
[Cmn] of course of Faith if in my embassy didn't help me with anything. I tried to
Explain [to] them they [called] my people. They said no they turn of my old man day
I came, and then I crouched remain of [God]. There's one thing [that's] I'm asking a man of course who help
Please help men of God
Empty step psychologically, I don't know I can't face people anymore
The time [that's] [I'm] going in the during the day. I can't go for three years. I'm in [tall's] I can't go else
I don't see their lies. I'm out. I quite round 12 a.m.. In the night. I don't also see anybody. I'm shaking I'm panicking
If in my degree, I don't know what you start to apply
I don't I don't [have] [any] vision only three many modulus is happening about my life, please deliver me
Your pillow are looking for you everywhere. [you] [are] spoiling. The name of your country and your [family]
So we are going to give our [ticket]
Money to go back at the same time
I want to speak to her didn't they have to take your far and forgive her. She has learned from a mistake. [she]
[is] not only going to be delivered the ministry is also
Interested in what you'll be doing when you go back to South Africa
if it does deliver an asset to go back
She was Chief, Oba
because economic may down
So she needs to be restored
complete restoration
My name is armand from South Africa. I came here to thank God for my deliverance I've
been delivered from the spirits of
Drinking and I tolls it's [destroyed] my life in everything. You know according [to] nothing for three years
I mean tours. I don't see people. I'm sleeping everyday
I'm lazy
Even to talk the way you can see I'm slowly I can no to anything simple rags as a woman I cannot do anything I
Wanted to go in the [evening] just to be alone in our pee talking at all sitting in the push
I don't care upon my future. I didn't mind. I'm a first palma family
they were all depending on me, but I tell him [que] I
Didn't Kj of my degree and everything all I was carrying this to eat and sleep
Lazy [I] can wash for myself to go into your head. I can't do anything now
I am quite an untelevised. I feel like something has come out of my brain
I feel confident again so [Kasey] the reason why God brought our here
Huh?
So to be delivered not even issue of ticket
Money for ticket is nothing anybody can give the money for ticket anybody can give our money to establish
Her somewhere, but to deliver her that is [America]
And I want to believe you value her deliverance because we pass through
King and tink
so to get his deliverance, so she'll be given a ticket and
To go back to our country and to come back
in Aris [Russia]
To to share her testimony with you
[ok] so she's here
Thank you, Jesus yaba. My chest my chest yeah born on December 1st. Thank you professor Patricia
Thank you. Thank you
Thank you
Yeah, bong bong bong and Cosimo Casaba lasagna gon be a Davenport Gonna feed you sedated in Estrogen [Famiiy]. [L]
Asamdigdha Mildew lockup, Escondido sabe [allocate] the [patents] on pieces I've got a pair on port Organa petrov economical I bought on eBay
Oh show Julia. I stole a delivery and she should also be given
$2,000 to go back zama once a bad girl realized her mistake
Stranded with no money to return home after her deliverance prophet TB
Joshua bought her an air ticket to return home to her parents in South Africa whom she had run [away] from two years ago
Prophet TB. Joshua Also gave her the sum of
$2,000 to assist her in making a fresh start in life
Her past now over and her bag packed
[zama] is ready to go and she looks forward to a new lease of life a new future and new life in Christ, Jesus
Let's hear from her. My name is Amin. Wa Nezzie. I'm from South Africa. I've not been paid to South Africa for three years
So I prophesied [it's] I'm a bad calif disappointed my appearance, and it's true the man of God promised me
You would buy me [a] [ticket] [sand] the mind for the business to start something
Not only that it's [also] to live like and now I have a ticket and the men of God give me
$2,000 to go instead something in South Africa
um plays blessed indeed she dips her hand into the bag and pulls out the
$2,000 and a ticket, I'm sorry I peter I'm going back to my [parents] for tree as I don't see them
I'm sorry appearance to thank the men of God for rescue my life, [va] I was almost a dead person, but no, I'm okay
I'm tilly [veidt] when God is involved in your matter your matter is settled
This is a far cry from someone who was once roaming about on the street living an aimless life
Jesus Christ can change anyone anytime
Anywhere, yes even zama glory be to God her history has been rewritten her story has changed
Yeah, by my chest yeah, Bourgogne bunga
You rescue me Lord, Jesus christ from this piece of handing a bomb and [positives] about my [profits] [Patricia]. Thank you
[I] was you again in Future. I promise I'll make you proud
God proud in my parents proud. I thank you so
Much from rescuing her from what she referred to as a piece of hell
Zama has made life's biggest decision to serve Jesus Christ
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you [have] just watched
click here to subscribe to witness more of god's power at work in our generation today, and
Stay up to date [with] the latest
prophecies
deliverances sermons and testimonies from the synagogue church of all nations
[Emmanuelle] TV changing lives changing nations and [changing] the world